Guide to the Time Inc. Staff Organizations 1940-2015 MS 3009-RG 18
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Staff Organizations
1940-2015
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 18
11.5 Linear feet in 11 record cartons, 2 flat boxes
Time Inc. Staff Organizations contains records from clubs, sports, and other membership organizations involving only Time Inc. staff. The organizations include the Time Inc. Bowling League, Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner (LGTW), and the Time-Life Alumni Society.
Scope and Contents Note
Time Inc. Staff Organizations contains records from clubs, sports, and other membership organizations involving only Time Inc. staff. These organizations were not necessarily sanctioned or overseen by Time Inc., but rather staff-driven. The organizations include the Time Inc. Bowling League, Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner (LGTW), and the Time-Life Alumni Society (TLAS).
Arrangement Note
Organized into three series:
Series I. Bowling League Records
Series II. Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner (LGTW) Records
Series III. Time-Life Alumni Society (TLAS) Collection
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials include membership information in Series II. Restricted materials are located in boxes R14. Materials created within the past 35 years also may be subject to restriction on a case-by-case basis. Unreformatted digital material in the collection is not accessible. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library. Additional records on Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner are in the Time Inc. Reference Files (MS 3009-RG 3).
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Bowling; Corporations -- History; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Gay community -- New York (State) -- New York; Lesbians -- Societies, etc.; Lesbian community -- New York (State) -- New York; Newsletters.; Photograph albums.; Organization files; Publishers and publishing -- Employees -- Recreation -- New York (State) -- New York; Publishers and publishing -- Employees -- Societies, etc.; Recreation -- New York (State) -- New York; Scrapbooks.; Team bowling; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- Employees -- Recreation; Time, inc. -- History
- Series I. Bowling League Records, 1961-1971, undated; 194304; 4.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons, 2 flat boxes
  Scope and Contents Note
  The Bowling League Records document Time Inc.'s staff bowling league from 1961 to 1971. Based on the records, members in charge at various times were Bud Bliven, Carol-Ann Carpentieri, Joyce Christiansen, Loretta Geissler, Rod McDonald, Mary Piper, Val Pour, and Marian Powers. While teams list both men and women members, there are some records for the Woman's Bowling League from the same time period. Records include lists of participants; certifications and sanctions from the national bowling organizations; invitations and planning materials for league luncheons, awards banquets, and the 25th anniversary; newsletters and flyers; record books containing scores, statistics, and schedules; scorecards; registration sheets; photographic material; a scrapbook; a photograph album; and buttons. The "General" files may contain any of these materials. The newsletter was at one point called b.i.f., which was the motto "Bowling is Fun," and looks styled after the Time Inc. newsletter F.Y.I. The folder "Old Time Inc. Bowlers" includes lists of participants going back to the 1950s.
  Arrangement Note
  Organized chronologically by bowling season, then alphabetically by topic or record type. Undated materials are at the end.
  - 1961/1962 Season: General, 194305 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 1-2)
  - 1962/1963 Season: General, 194306 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 3, 5-6)
  - 1962/1963 Season: Luncheon, 194929 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 4)
  - 1963/1964 Season: General, 194307 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 7-9)
  - 1963/1964 Season: Banquet, 194308 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 10)
  - 1963/1964 Season: Scorecards and Reports, 194309 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 11-12)
  - 1964/1965 Season: General, 194310 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 13-14)
  - 1964/1965 Season: Banquet, 194311 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 15)
  - 1964/1965 Season: Luncheon, 194312 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 16)
  - 1964/1965 Season: Newsletter, 194313 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 17-19)
  - 1964/1965 Season: Scorecards, 194314 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 20)
  - 1965/1966 Season: General, 194315 (Offsite-box 787, Folder 21-24)
  - 1965/1966 Season: Banquet, 194316 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 1)
  - 1965/1966 Season: Luncheon, 194317 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 2)
  - 1965/1966 Season: Record Book, 194318 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 3-4)
  - 1966/1967 Season: Luncheon, 194319 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 5)
  - 1966/1967? Season: Record Book, approximately 1966; 194321 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 6-7)
  - 1967/1968 Season: American Bowling Congress Certificate, 194322 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 8)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Banquet Information, 194323 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 9-10)
  - 1967/1968? Season: League Sanctioning, approximately 1967; 194324 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 11)
  - 1967/1968 Season: League Secretary's Workbook and Planner, 194325 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 12-13)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Newsletter, 194326 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 14)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Record Book, 194327 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 15)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Registration Cards, 194328 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 16)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Scorecards, 194329 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 17)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Team Information, 194330 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 18)
  - 1967/1968 Season: 25th Anniversary, 194331 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 19-20)
  - 1967/1968 Season: Women's International Bowling Congress Santioning, 194332 (Offsite-box 788, Folder 21)
  - 1968/1969 Season: American Bowling Congress Certificate, 194333 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 1)
  - 1968/1969 Season: Luncheon, 194334 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 2)
  - 1968/1969 Season: Old Time Inc. Bowlers, 194335 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 3-4)
  - 1968/1969 Season: Scorecards, 194336 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 5)
  - 1969/1970 Season: Sanctioning, 194337 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 6)
  - 1969/1970 Season: Scorecards, 194338 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 7-8)
  - 1970/1971 Season: Scrapbook, 194346 (Offsite-box 790, Folder 1)
  - Blank Award Cards, undated; 194339 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 9)
  - Bowling Images, undated; 194340 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 10)
  - Brochure and Flyer Mock-Ups, undated; 194344 (Offsite-box 1481, Folder 1)
  - Buttons, undated; 194343 (Offsite-box 789)
  - Flyer or Invitation Mockups, undated; 215047 (Offsite-box 1481, Folder 2)
  - Photograph Album, undated; 194345 (Offsite-box 790, Folder 2)
    Photographs are of an event at Mamma Leone's.
  - Photographs and Negatives, undated; 194341 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 11)
  - Sketches, undated; 194342 (Offsite-box 789, Folder 12)
- Series II. Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner (LGTW) Records, 1988-1997; 194903; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Biographical/Historical Note
  Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner (LGTW) was a staff grassroots organization at Time Warner from 1990 to 1995. Its goal was to be an "education and support group that addresses workplace issues affecting employees who are lesbian, gay, or bisexual". Later iterations of the group include Out@TimeWarner and Out@TimeInc.
  Records include advocacy correspondence, meeting agenda, membership cards and contact lists, event planning materials, newsletters, memoranda, news clippings, and reference material. Membership lists and other materials naming members other than the Coordinating Committee are restricted since member confidentiality was assured by the group.
  Organized chronologically by year, then alphabetically by topic or record type. Undated materials are at the beginning.
  - New member cards [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 194944 (Offsite-box R14)
  - General Reference, 1988-1994; 194910 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 1)
  - AT&T, 1990; 194908 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 2)
  - Canned Food Drive, 1990; 194909 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 3)
  - Christmas Party, 1990; 194911 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 4)
  - Christmas Party [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 194937 (Offsite-box R14)
  - GLAAD Media Guide to the Lesbian and Gay Community, 1990; 194907 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 5)
  - Announcements, 1990-1991; 194912 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 6)
  - Contact Information [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1990-1991; 194934 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Contact List [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1990-1995; 194941 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda/Agendas, 1990-1995; 194905 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda/Agendas [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1990-1995; 194933 (Offsite-box R14)
  - AIDS Walk, 1991; 194915 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Walk [RESTRICTED], 199326 (Offsite-box R14)
    Includes digital material of 1 computer disc (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in.
  - And The Band Played On Script, 1991; 194904 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 9-10)
  - Bergalis, Kimberly: Time Magazine [Article], 1991; 194916 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 11)
  - Christmas Party, 1991; 194917 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Party [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1991; 194936 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Domestic Partnership Meeting I, 1991; 194918 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 13)
  - Heritage of Pride, 1991; 194928 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 14)
  - Spring Gala, 1991; 194914 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 15)
  - Spring Gala [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1991; 194935 (Offsite-box R14)
  - World AIDS Day, 1991; 194913 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 16)
  - Holiday Party, 1992; 194921 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 17)
  - Holiday Party [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1992; 194938 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Summer Update, 1992; 194919 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 18)
  - Time Warner Work & Family Resource Area, 1992; 194920 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 19)
  - World AIDS Day, 1992; 194922 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 20)
  - World AIDS Day [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1992; 194942 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Current Materials, 1992-1993; 194923 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1992-1994; 194906 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 22)
  - AIDS Walk, 1993; 194924 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 23)
  - Holiday Party, 1993; 194925 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 24)
  - World AIDS Day, 1993; 194926 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1993; 194927 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 26)
  - Announcements and Memos, 1993-1994; 194930 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 27-28)
  - Coming Out Day [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2072], 1994; 194943 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Announcements and Memos, 1994; 194931 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 29-31)
  - Reflections and Responses, 1997; 194932 (Offsite-box 826, Folder 32)
- Series III. Time-Life Alumni Society (TLAS) Collection, 1940-2015; 6 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
  Biographical / Historical
  The Time-Life Alumni Society (TLAS) was founded in October 1977 by several retiring editors as a way to keep former Time Inc. employees connected to Time Inc. and each other after leaving the company. Receiving a small stipend by Time Inc. to print invitations and a newsletter, as well as office space, TLAS used member dues to fund several luncheons with guest speakers per year prior to 2018. Notable members include Dick Stolley, Norm Pearlstine, John Huey, Ralph Graves, and Maureen Dowd.
  Scope and Contents
  Materials include videocassettes, audiocassettes, photographs, member directories, memos, meeting minutes, newsletters, news clippings, and correspondence. These are records gathered by the Time Inc. Archives from TLAS and do not reflect TLAS's original organizational records.
  Arrangement
  Organized into five subseries:
  Subseries III.A. President's Files
  Subseries III.B. Newsletters and Membership Directories
  Subseries III.C. Photographs
  Subseries III.D. Audiovisual materials
  Subseries III.E. General
  - Subseries III.A. President's Files, 1980-2005; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Dick Stolley, whose materials from time as TLAS president are included, was an editor at various Time Inc. publications for over 40 years. His most notable moment was when he, as Life magazine editor, negotiated to purchase rights to the Zapruder film of the Kennedy assassination. Materials are dated from 2000 to 2005 and contain materials such as news clippings or personal letters from TLAS members, obituaries regarding past TLAS members, and internal correspondence or memos regarding TLAS activities.
    Arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Directory of Members, 2005 (Offsite-box 2786, Folder 1)
    - Time-Life Alumni Society Miscellaneous, 2001-2004 (Offsite-box 2786, Folder 2-9)
    - Time-Life Alumni Society AOL Deal, 2001 (Offsite-box 2786, Folder 10-11)
    - Time-Life Alumni Society Miscellaneous, 2000 (Offsite-box 2786, Folder 12-14)
    - Luncheon Guests, 1980-2007 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 1)
    - Carky Rubens Poster, undated (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 2)
  - Subseries III.B. Newsletters And Membership Directories, 1979-2015; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    The member directories and newsletters range from 1979 to 2015. Newsletters also contain extra souvenir pamphlets from TLAS-sponsored parties or "Travels with TLAS".
    Arranged alphabetically, then in reverse chronological order within each group.
    - Membership Directories, 1978-2011 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 3-7)
    - Newsletters, 1977-2015 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 8-10)
  - Subseries III.C. Photographs, 1940-1988; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Most of the photographs are of TLAS parties or "Travels with TLAS", which consisted of tours in locations such as Storm King, Paris, and Washington, D.C. One set of photographs, from the now-defunct 1940s employee group Time Out, is from Daniel and Mary Fraser Longwell's personal collection, sent to Marian McDermott in 1978; Daniel helped found Life magazine and was an editor for ten years, and Mary was a chief of research at Time (Prendergast and Colvin 449). Please note this Time Out group is not associated with the later LGBT staff organization.
    Arranged in reverse chronological, with undated materials at the end.
    - 1988: April Bash (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 15)
    - 1988 April: Ralph Crane Memorial (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 16)
    - 1988 April: Paris Tour Photos (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 1)
    - 1987 October: Unknown event (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 2)
    - 1987 June 27: West Coast Cocktail Party: Photographed by Ben Martin (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 3)
    - 1987: Paris Bash (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 4-5)
    - 1987: Paris Tour: Photographed By Walter Daren (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 6)
    - 1986 October 8: New York Bash II (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 7)
    - 1986 June 3-5: Travels With TLAS: Washington, D.C. and Mt. Vernon (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 8-9)
    - 1986: Unknown event (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 10)
    - 1985 May 13-14: Travels With TLAS: Longwood Gardens, Brandywine Museum and Winterthorn: Photographed By Sandra Streapy (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 11)
    - 1986 June 4: Washington Bash (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 12)
    - 1985 December: Los Angeles Party (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 13)
    - 1982-1985: Travels with TLAS: Delaware, Maryland, and Virginia (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 14)
    - 1984 September 19-20: Travels With TLAS: A Connecticut Adventure: Photographed By Shelley Mydan (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 15)
    - 1984 May 14-16: Travels With TLAS: Eastern Shore, Annapolis, Baltimore: Photographed by John Florea (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 16)
    - 1983 September 29: Travels With TLAS: Storm King Art Center and Boscobel: Photographed By Harry Harding (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 17)
    - 1982 October 19-21: Travels With TLAS: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 18)
    - 1981: Luncheon With Guest Speaker Murray Gart (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 19)
    - 1979-1983: California Reunion Photo Spread (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 20)
    - 1979 October 18: TLAS Bash II (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 21)
    - 1979 March 15: West Palm Beach Reunion (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 22)
    - 1978 April 20: TLAS Bash I (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 23)
    - 1941-1987: Longwell "Time Out" Photographs (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 24-25)
    - Undated: Paris Bash: Photographed By Walter Doran (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 26)
    - Undated: Unused Bash Photos: Photographed By Martha Holmes (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 27)
    - Undated: Unknown Event (Offsite-box 2788, Folder 28)
  - Subseries III.D. Audiovisual materials [RESTRICTED], 1985-2001; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Videocassettes are recordings of TLAS luncheon presentations and panels. Notable speakers include Hugh Sidey, Dick Stolley, Norm Pearlstine, and Martha Stewart.
    The audiocassettes are recordings of TLAS luncheon presentations.
    Arranged by subject of event, then by speakers.
    - Loose cassette labels, 1993 (Offsite-box 2787, Folder 14)
    - Anniversary: People 20th Anniversary, 1994 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 1)
      1 videocassette. On label: "Time Life Alumni - People 20th Anniv 2/23/94".
    - Anniversary: Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue 25th Anniversary, 1989 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 2)
      1 videocassette. On label: "TLAS - S.I. 25th Anniv. of Swimsuit Iss. 2/21/89".
    - Anniversary: Time-Life Alumni Society 10th Anniversary Bash, 1986 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 3)
      1 videocassette. On label: "Time Life Alumni - 10th Anniv. Bash 10/8/86 (partially inaudible)".
    - Anniversary: Time Life Alumni Society 20th Anniversary Party, 1996 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 4)
      1 videocassette. On label: "Time Life Alumni Society 20th Anniversary Party November 20th, 1996".
    - Luncheon: Cloud, Stanley, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 5-10)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Time Life Alumni Society - Stanley Cloud, Hays Gorey, Alessandra Stanley on 1988 Election Candidates 6/8/88".
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "TLAS Luncheon - Panel from TIME's Washington Bureau: Cloud, Stanley; Carlson, Margaret; Duffy, Michael 12/2/92".
      2 videocassettes (VHS). On label: "Time-EDIT Washington Bureau Panel - TLAS luncheon 'Election' - Cloud, Duffy, Carlson 12/2/92".
      2 videocassettes (U-matic). On label: "TLAS luncheon - Washington correspondents - The election - Cloud, Barrett, Goodgame 6/4/92 (Parts I and II)".
    - Luncheon: Fuchs, Michael, 1985 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 1)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Fuchs, Michael - Speech Time Life - Alumni Luncheon 9/10/85." Label on Side 1: "Side 1 M. Fuchs (HBO) Time Inc. Alumni Speech Sept. 10, 1985." Label on Side 2: "Side 2."
    - Luncheon: Grunwald, Harry, 1985 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 2)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Grunwald - speech TLAS 1/4/85." Label on Side 1: "#1 T/L Aud. - Grunwald 1-4-85." Label on Side 2: "#2"
    - Luncheon: Loeb, Marshall, 1988 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 3-4)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Loeb, Marshall - TLAS Meeting 10/19/88." Label on container: "TLAS Meeting 10/19/88. Anne Moore re: SI for Kid, Fortune ME; Loeb, Marshall 'One Year After The Crash'." Label on Side 1: "Anne Moore, Marshall Loeb TLAS meeting 10/19/88."
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Loeb, Marshall TLAS 10/19/88." Label on Side 2: "Loeb, Marshall TLAS (partial) 10/19/88."
    - Luncheon: Pearlstine, Norman, 1995 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 10-12)
      1 videocassette. On label: "Pearlstine, Norman. Time Life Alumni Society Luncheon 2/21/95. VO438".
      2 videocassettes. On label: "Pearlstine, Norman. Time Life Alumni Society Luncheon 2/21/95. VO438 (dup)".
    - Luncheon: Prendergast, Whipple, 1986 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 5-6)
      2 audiocassettes: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1 of both tapes: "Prendergast, Whipple - TLAS (dup) 6/26/1986".
    - Luncheon: Rosenblatt, Roger, 1993 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 13-15)
      3 videocassettes. On labels: "Rosenblatt, Roger. "Freedom of Speech" Time Life Alumni Speaker 2/18/93".
    - Luncheon: Ross, Steven, 1989 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 16-19)
      3 videocassettes (U-matic). On label: "Ross, Steven, Speech TLAS luncheon, Re: Warner and merger 11/7/89"
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Ross, Steven, Speech TLAS luncheon, Re: Warner and merger 11/7/89, Copy from Time".
    - Luncheon: Rowan, Roy, 1996 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 20-21)
      2 videocassettes (VHS). On label: "Time Life Alumni Society Wednesday April 24, 1996".
    - Luncheon: Ryan, Patricia, 1987 (Offsite-box 2789, Item 22)
      1 videocassette (U-Matic). On label: "Ryan, Patricia - Life Me, TLAS Luncheon 2/1/87".
    - Luncheon: Ryan, Patricia, 1987 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Ryan, Patricia - Time-Life-Alumni Luncheon Speech 5/1/87".
    - Luncheon: Sagan, Paul, 1993 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Time Life Alumni Luncheon, New York News - Channel #1, Paul Sagan 10/7/1993".
    - Luncheon: Schecter, Jerrold, 1994 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 3-4)
      2 videocassettes (VHS). On label: "Schecter, Jerrold TLAS Luncheon 9/28/94. Book, '...Soviet Spymaster'".
    - Luncheon: Sidey, Hugh, 1990-2001 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 5-7)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Sidey, Hugh, Time Life Alumni Speaker (partial tape) 12/5/90".
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "2/15/01 Hugh Sidey TLAS".
      1 videocassette (U-matic). On label: "Sidey, Hugh Time Life Alumni Speaker (partial tape) 12/5/90".
    - Luncheon: Stacks, John, 1991 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 8-9)
      2 videocassettes (VHS). On label: "Stacks, John - TLAS Luncheon - Coverage of Gulf War 3/11/91".
    - Luncheon: Stewart, Martha, 1994 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 10-11)
      2 videocassettes (VHS). On label: "TLAS - Luncheon, Martha Stewart 6/8/94".
    - Luncheon: Stolley, Richard, 1985 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 7-8)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "Stolley - Speech TLAS 11/1985." Label on Side 1: "TLAS - Richard Stolley."
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: ""Stolley, Richard TLAS (dup) - 'Picture Week' 11/85." Label on Side 1: "TLAS - Richard Stolley 11/85." Label on Side 2: "TLAS - Stolley cont. TLAS lunch."
    - Luncheon: Sutton, Kelso F., 1986 (Offsite-box 2215, Item 9)
      /1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on container: "T/L Alumni 5-29-86 Kelso F. Sutton." Label on Side 1: "T/L Alumni copy 5/29/86."
    - Luncheon: Talbott, Strobe, 1990 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 12-13)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Talbott, Strobe TLAS Luncheon 3/13/90".
      1 videocassette (U-matic). On label: "Talbott, Strobe TLAS Luncheon 3/13/90".
    - Luncheon: Time Warner Merger, 1989 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (U-matic). On label: "Time Warner Merger TLAS Luncheon Presentation 4/12/89".
    - Luncheon: Turner, Ted, 1997 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS). On label: "Time-Life Alumni Society Ted Turner lunch June 25, 1997".
    - Luncheon: Unknown speaker, undated (Offsite-box 2215, Item 10)
      1 audiocassette: analog, 1 5/16 ips, stereo; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. Label on Side 1: "II."
    - Luncheon: Washington Panel, 1992-2000 (Offsite-box 2790, Item 16-17)